Guide to the Whitney Humanities Center, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Committee records, 1978-1982; Accession 1989-A-003
  - Minutes of Meetings, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Miscellaneous, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Music, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Near Eastern Languages, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Philosophy, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Religious Studies, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Slavics Department, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Spanish & Portuguese, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Special Programs, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Theater Studies, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Women's Studies, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Humanities, Division of Director, 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Humanities Report, 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Academic Review Committee, 1979-82 (Box 2, Folder 57-59)
  - ARC: Recommendations of Faculty Promotions, 1980-81 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Cognitive Science, 1980-81 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Editorial Projects at Yale, 1979-82 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Executive Committee: Faculty of Science, 1979-82 (Box 3, Folder 63-64)
  - Hartman Memorandum, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Provostial Correspondence, 1979-82 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- Records, 1951-1987; Accession 1989-A-026
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2023.
  - Scholars of the House
    - Director's Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Senior Essay Extension for Vincent Peterson, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Expenses, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Budget Statements, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Examinations Schedule, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - General Information, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Production Costs, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Prospective Scholars, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Alumni Magazine Article, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence (Official and Personal), 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Expenses, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Prospective Scholars, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - General Information, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Recommendations for Students, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Official Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - #1 of 2 Expenses and Budget, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - #2 of 2 Expenses and Budget, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - General Information, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Prospective Scholars, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Recommendations for Students, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Expenses, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Expenses, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence (Official and Personal), 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - History, The Arts and Letters
    - Student Grades, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - HAL 70 Syllabus, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - HAL 70 Accepted Applications, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - HAL 70 Rejected Applications, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Class Lists and Student Information, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous, Poetry, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Fall Syllabi, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - HAL 80 Accepted Applications, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - HAL 80 Rejected Applications, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Colloquia, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Senior Essays Prospectus, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Transcripts, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Kilborne Scholarship, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Syllabi, Spring, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - HAL 80 Information, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - HAL 90 Information, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Transcripts, Class of 1967, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Transcripts, Class of 1968, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Miscellaneous, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Applications, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Comprehensive Exams, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Kilborne Scholarship, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Student Survey, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Budget, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Director's Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Junior Seminar, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Senior Essays and Exams, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Budget, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Bursary Employment, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Committee on Majors, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Special Programs in the Humanities
    - Director's Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - History, The Arts and Letters
    - Class of 1969, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Transcripts, Class of 1971, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Directed Studies
    - #1 of 2 Transcripts, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - #2 of 2 Transcripts, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Student and Faculty Lists, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Courses, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Course Evaluations, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Student and Faculty Lists, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Budget, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Director's Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Personnel Profiles, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Personnel Profiles, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Senior Seminar, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Departmental Exams, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Honors and Distinction, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Kilborne Memorial Scholarship, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Class of 1969, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Director's Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Enrollment and Grades, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Bursary Employment, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Official Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Class of 1970, 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Budget, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Kilborne Scholarship, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Class of 1970, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Honors and Distinction, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Junior Seminar, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Budget, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Bursary EmploYment, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Official Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Personnel Profiles, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Class of 1971, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Departmental Exams, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Enrollment and Grade Lists, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Honors and Distinction, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Kilborne Scholarship, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Miscellaneous, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Senior Performance, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Syllabi, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Student Lists, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Description of the Major, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Requirements of the Major, 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Requirements of the Major, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - Schedules, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Review of Student Majors, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Senior Essays, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Colloquia, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - Senior Essay Evaluations, 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Sophomore Seminar, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - Departmental Examinations, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Sophomore Seminar, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Enrollment and Records, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - Syllabi, 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Junior Examinations, 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - Enrollment and Records, 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Senior Essay Prospectus, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - Senior Essay Evaluations, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Applications and Enrollment, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Senior Essays and Honors Reports, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Junior Seminar Information, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Departmental Examinations, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Committee Meetings, 1957-1963 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Senior Essays and Honors Reports, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Junior Seminar, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Senior Seminar, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Departmental Exams, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - Kilborne Scholarship, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Junior Seminar, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - Senior Seminar, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Departmental Exams, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Kilborne Scholarship, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - Honors, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - Enrollment, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Official Correpondence, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - Departmental Exams, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - Senior Essays, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - Junior Seminar, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 131)
  - Directed Studies
    - Class and Faculty Lists, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - #1 of 2 Transcripts, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - #2 of 2 Transcripts, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - Student Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - Courses, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - Budget Statements, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - Personnel Profiles, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - Official Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - History, The Arts and Letters
    - Enrollment, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - Transcripts, Class of 1972, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - Official Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - Honors, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - Kilborne Scholarship, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - #1 of 2 Program Syllabi, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - #2 of 2 Program Syllabi, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - Class Lists, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - Personnel Profiles, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - Bursary EmploYment, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - Official Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - Personnel Profiles, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - Merger Proposal, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - Statistics, Class of 1973, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 154)
    - Class and Faculty Lists, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 155)
    - Sophomore Seminar, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 156)
    - #1 of 2 Applications for Sophomore Seminar, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 157)
    - #2 of 2 Applications for Sophomore Seminar, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 158)
    - Sophomore Seminar Accepted Applications, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 159)
    - Reports on Senior Essays, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 160)
    - Kilborne Scholarship, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 161)
    - Transcripts, Class of 1973, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 162)
    - Syllabi, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 163)
    - Sophomore Seminar Rejected Applications, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 164)
  - Special Programs in the Humanities
    - Audio-Visual, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 165)
    - Receipts, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 166)
    - Bursary Employment, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 167)
    - Purchase Orders, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 168)
    - Requests for Stocks, Services, and Checks, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 169)
    - Course of Study Information, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 170)
    - Official Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 171)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 172)
    - Faculty Information, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 173)
    - Fair Labor Standards Act Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 174)
    - Governing Board, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 175)
    - Chart of Accounts, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 176)
    - Personnel Profiles, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 177)
    - Special Functions, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 178)
  - Directed Studies
    - Transcripts, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 179)
    - Faculty and Class Lists, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 180)
    - Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 181)
    - Personnel Profiles, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 182)
    - Official Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 183)
  - British Studies
    - General Information, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 184)
  - History, The Arts and Letters
    - Budget, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 185)
    - Cost Transfers, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 186)
    - Purchase Orders, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 187)
    - Requests for Checks, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 188)
    - Stock Requests, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 189)
    - Catalogue Copy, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 190)
    - Personnel Profiles, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 191)
    - Contracts, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 192)
    - #1 of 2 Official Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 193)
    - #2 of 2 Official Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 194)
    - #1 of 3 Director's Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 195)
    - #2 of 3 Director's Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 196)
    - #3 of 3 Director's Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 197)
    - Faculty Information, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 198)
    - Fair Labor Standards Act Report, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 199)
    - Historical Data, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 200)
    - Meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 201)
    - Publicity, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 202)
    - Calendar, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 203)
    - Syllabi, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 204)
    - Faculty Credits, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 205)
    - Grades, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 206)
    - Deskcopy Orders, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 207)
    - Course Book Requisitions, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 208)
    - Francis E. Riggs Prize, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 209)
    - History, The Arts and Letters, 1938-1976 (Box 5, Folder 210)
    - Class Lists, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 211)
    - Final Examinations, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 212)
    - Humanities 70 Applications, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 213)
    - Humanities 80 Applications, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 214)
    - Humanities 90 Colloquia, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 215)
    - Humanities 97, The Senior Essay, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 216)
    - Syllabi, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 217)
    - Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 218)
    - Guest Lecturers, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 219)
    - Cost Transfers, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 220)
    - Personnel Profiles, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 221)
    - Purchase Orders, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 222)
    - Request for Checks, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 223)
    - Stock and Service Requests, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 224)
    - Catalogue Copy, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 225)
    - Class Lists, 1967-1972 (Box 5, Folder 226)
    - Faculty, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 227)
    - Paul Mellon Fund, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 228)
    - Miscellaneous, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 229)
    - Secretary, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 230)
    - Yale College Programs of Study: Supplements, 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 231)
  - Directed Studies
    - Documentary History, 1946-1976 (Box 5, Folder 232)
  - History, The Arts and Letters
    - Class Lists, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 233)
    - Grade Lists, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 234)
    - HAL 80 Assignments, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 235)
    - Prospectuses for Senior Essays, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 236)
    - HAL 90 Assignments, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 237)
    - HAL 90 Miscellaneous, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 238)
    - Honors and Distinction, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 239)
    - Kilborne Scholarship, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 240)
    - Senior Essay Evaluations, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 241)
    - Transcripts, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 242)
    - Wrexham Prize, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 243)
    - Syllabi, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 244)
    - Class Lists, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 245)
    - Final Examinations, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 246)
    - Senior Essay Grades, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 247)
    - Honors and Distinction, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 248)
    - Kilborne Scholarship, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 249)
    - Enrollment, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 250)
    - Curriculum Vitae, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 251)
    - Transcripts, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 252)
    - HAL 70 Applications, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 253)
    - HAL 70 Assignments, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 254)
    - HAL 80 Applications, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 255)
    - HAL 80 Miscellaneous, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 256)
    - HAL 80 Final Examination, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 257)
    - HAL 90 Assignments, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 258)
    - Prospectuses for Senior Essays, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 259)
    - Senior Essay Deadlines, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 260)
    - Senior Essay Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 261)
    - Syllabi, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 262)
  - Directed Studies
    - Class Lists, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 263)
    - Faculty Lists, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 264)
    - Reading Assignments, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 265)
    - Syllabi, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 266)
    - Grade Lists, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 267)
    - Francis E. Riggs Prize, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 268)
  - British Studies
    - 1974-1975 (British Studies) (Box 6, Folder 269)
  - Special Programs in the Humanities, Administration
    - Budget, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 270)
    - Cost Transfers, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 271)
    - Purchase Orders, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 272)
    - Requests for Checks and Services, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 273)
    - Statements of Account, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 274)
    - Stock Requests, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 275)
    - Catalogue Copy, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 276)
    - Director's Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 277)
    - Final Examinations, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 278)
    - Yale College Grading Policies, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 279)
    - Departmental Majors, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 280)
    - Directory Information, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 281)
    - Faculty, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 282)
    - Departmental Credits, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 283)
    - Faculty Recruitment, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 284)
    - Fair Labor Standards Act, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 285)
    - Governing Board, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 286)
    - Guest Lecturers, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 287)
    - IBM: Sales and Service, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 288)
    - Major Subjects, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 289)
    - Meetings and Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 290)
    - Personnel Profiles, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 291)
    - Personnel Profiles: Guest Lecturers, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 292)
    - Secretary's Personnel Profile, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 293)
    - Student EmploYment, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 294)
    - Student Enrollment, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 295)
    - Yale College Programs of Study Information, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 296)
    - Class Lists, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 297)
  - Scholars of the House
    - Director's Miscellaneous ,Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 298)
    - Director's Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 299)
    - Miscellaneous, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 310)
    - Project Grades, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 311)
    - Adviser Evaluations, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 312)
    - Program Reviews, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 313)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 324)
    - Director's Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 325)
  - Directed Studies
    - Statistical Data, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 326)
    - Successful Applicants, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 327)
    - Grades, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 328)
    - Waiting List, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 329)
    - Official Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 330-331)
    - Final Exams, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 332)
    - Director's Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 333)
    - Miscellaneous, 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 334)
    - Administrative Material, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 335)
    - Francis Riggs Prize, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 336)
    - Student Evaluations, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 337)
    - Syllabi, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 338)
  - History, The Arts and Letters
    - Director's Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 339)
    - Kilborne Scholarship, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 340)
    - HAL 270 Applications, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 341-343)
    - HAL 270 Miscellaneous, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 344)
    - Undergraduate Statistics, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 345)
    - Publicity, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 346)
    - Recommendations, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 347)
    - Syllabi, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 348)
    - HAL 380 Miscellaneous, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 349)
    - HAL 380 Applications, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 350-351)
    - HAL 489 Miscellaneous, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 352)
    - Comprehensive Examinations, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 353)
    - Honors and Distinction, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 354)
    - Senior Essay Colloquia, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 355)
    - Recommendation for New Courses, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 356)
    - Senior Essay Readers, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 357)
    - Senior Essay Drafts, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 358)
    - Senior Essay Prospectus, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 359)
    - Budget Statements, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 360)
  - Directed Studies
    - Faculty Lists, 1976-1981 (Box 8, Folder 361)
  - British Studies
    - Miscellaneous, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 362)
  - Special Programs in the Humanities, Administration
    - Class Schedules, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 363)
    - Director's Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 364-365)
    - Executive Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 366)
    - Student Evaluations, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 367)
    - Lewis Curtis Fund, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 368)
    - Faculty Lists, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 369)
    - Faculty, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 370)
    - Prize Nominations, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 371)
    - Bulletin Information, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 372)
    - Budget Negotiations, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 373)
    - Bulletin Information, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 374)
    - Classroom Allocation, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 375)
    - Director's Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 376)
    - Faculty Information, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 377)
    - Departmental Credits, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 378)
    - Budget Statements, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 379)
    - Receipts and Purchase Orders, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 380)
    - Governing Board, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 381)
    - Majors List, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 382)
  - Directed Studies
    - Course Book Requisitions, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 383)
    - Syllabi, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 384)
    - Colloquia, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 385)
    - Applications, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 386-390)
    - Waiting List, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 391)
    - Student Lists, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 392)
    - Student Grades, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 393)
    - Applicant Statistics, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 394)
    - Miscellaneous, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 395)
    - Majors List, 1974-1980 (Box 9, Folder 396)
    - Applications, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 397-402)
    - Waiting List, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 403)
    - Francis Riggs Prize, 1978-1980 (Box 9, Folder 404)
    - Colloquia, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 405)
    - Director's Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 406)
    - Philosophy I Evaluations, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 407)
    - Syllabi, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 408)
  - Special Programs in the Humanities, Administration
    - Classroom Allocations, 1979-1980. (Box 9, Folder 409)
    - Bulletin Information, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 410)
    - Director's Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 411)
    - Enrollment Statistics, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 412)
    - Faculty Information, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 413)
    - Budget Committments, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 414)
    - Governing Board, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 415)
  - History, The Arts and Letters
    - Committee on Core Curriculum, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 416)
    - Director's Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 417)
    - Course Book Requisitions, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 418)
    - Kilborne Prize, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 419)
    - Enrollment Statistics, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 420)
    - Recommendations, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 421)